[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 4) \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 2) \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "8",
        "5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 2) \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "16",
        "15",
        "14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (3 + 2) \u00d7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "17",
        "16",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 1) \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "7",
        "6",
        "5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 5) \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "10",
        "9",
        "11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 3) \u00d7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "16",
        "15",
        "17"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 5) \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "11",
        "14",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 1) \u00d7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "8",
        "5",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 1) \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "20",
      "options": [
        "21",
        "20",
        "19",
        "22"
      ]
    }
]